<resources>
    <string name="app_name">assignment-2</string>
    <string name="quote_day_1">Stay hydrated for better health.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_2">Take a brisk walk for 30 minutes.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_3">Eat more fruits and vegetables for essential nutrients.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_4">Practice mindfulness to reduce stress.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_5">Get at least 7-8 hours of sleep each night.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_6">Limit processed foods for a healthier diet.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_7">Do stretching exercises to increase flexibility.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_8">Maintain a regular exercise routine.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_9">Take deep breaths to calm your mind.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_10">Avoid smoking for better lung health.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_11">Drink green tea for antioxidants.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_12">Use stairs instead of elevators for extra activity.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_13">Practice good hygiene to prevent illness.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_14">Limit your sugar intake.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_15">Engage in regular cardiovascular exercise.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_16">Keep a positive attitude for mental health.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_17">Try yoga for both physical and mental benefits.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_18">Plan your meals for balanced nutrition.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_19">Avoid sitting for prolonged periods.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_20">Stay connected with loved ones for emotional health.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_21">Use sunscreen to protect your skin.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_22">Drink water instead of sugary drinks.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_23">Choose whole grains over refined grains.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_24">Take time for yourself to prevent burnout.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_25">Include protein in every meal.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_26">Practice gratitude to enhance wellbeing.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_27">Limit alcohol consumption.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_28">Seek medical advice when needed.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_29">Focus on portion control when eating.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_30">Celebrate your health achievements, no matter how small.</string>
    <string name="quote_day_31">Incorporate a new healthy habit into your routine each month.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_1">Hydration is crucial for maintaining good health. Drinking enough water each day helps regulate body temperature, keep joints lubricated, prevent infections, deliver nutrients to cells, and keep organs functioning properly. Being well-hydrated also improves sleep quality, cognition, and mood.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_2">A brisk 30-minute walk daily can improve cardiovascular health, strengthen bones, reduce excess body fat, and boost muscle power and endurance. It can also reduce your risk of developing conditions such as heart disease, type 2 diabetes, osteoporosis, and some cancers.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_3">Eating fruits and vegetables provides essential nutrients vital for health and maintenance of your body. They are rich in vitamins, minerals, and fiber and low in calories. Eating a variety of fruits and vegetables may help control weight and blood pressure.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_4">Mindfulness involves being fully engaged in the present moment. It can reduce stress and improve overall emotional health, leading to reduced anxiety, depression, and pain. Mindfulness meditation has also been linked with improved sleep and focus.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_5">Getting 7-8 hours of sleep per night is essential for your health. Quality sleep helps to repair your body, improves concentration and productivity, and reduces the risk of heart disease, stroke, diabetes, and obesity.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_6">Limiting processed foods can lead to improved overall health. These foods often contain unhealthy levels of added sugar, sodium, and fat, which can lead to obesity, heart disease, high blood pressure, and diabetes.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_7">Stretching exercises enhance flexibility, which increases your range of motion, reduces discomfort and the risk of injury, improves balance and coordination, and can even help relieve stress.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_8">Maintaining a regular exercise routine is crucial for overall health and well-being. It helps control weight, combats health conditions and diseases, improves mood, boosts energy, and promotes better sleep.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_9">Taking deep breaths helps calm your mind, reduce stress and anxiety, lower blood pressure, and even improve digestion. Deep breathing exercises are a simple yet effective way to improve your mental and physical wellbeing.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_10">Avoiding smoking is one of the best things you can do for your lung health. It lowers your risk of lung disease, heart disease, stroke, and cancer. Quitting smoking can add years to your life and significantly improve your overall quality of life.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_11">Green tea is rich in antioxidants that can improve brain function, aid fat loss, protect against cancer, and lower the risk of heart disease. Its bioactive compounds also have various protective effects on neurons.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_12">Using stairs instead of elevators can help you incorporate more physical activity into your daily routine. It strengthens your legs, improves cardiovascular health, and increases calorie burn, aiding in weight management.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_13">Practicing good hygiene is essential to prevent the spread of infectious diseases. Regular hand washing, maintaining clean surroundings, and personal hygiene can significantly reduce the risk of illness and infection.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_14">Limiting sugar intake can have numerous benefits for your health. It helps maintain a healthy weight, reduces the risk of heart disease, can improve your skin, and lowers the risk of diabetes.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_15">Regular cardiovascular exercise strengthens your heart and lungs, increases endurance, improves cholesterol and blood pressure, reduces the risk of heart disease, stroke, and diabetes, and helps manage weight.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_16">Keeping a positive attitude can help with mental and physical health. It can reduce stress, improve coping skills, increase resilience, lead to a longer life span, and improve overall wellbeing.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_17">Yoga offers various physical benefits, such as increased flexibility, muscle strength, and tone. It also helps in managing stress, calming the mind, improving mental well-being, and enhancing mindfulness.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_18">Planning your meals can help ensure you get a balanced diet with all the necessary nutrients. It can also help with weight control, save time, reduce food waste, and improve your relationship with food.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_19">Avoiding prolonged sitting can reduce the risk of chronic health issues like heart disease, diabetes, and obesity. Regular movement improves circulation, increases metabolism, and contributes to overall health.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_20">Staying connected with loved ones can improve emotional health by providing a sense of belonging and decreasing feelings of loneliness. It strengthens emotional support and can have a positive effect on mental health.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_21">Using sunscreen helps protect your skin from harmful UV rays, reducing the risk of skin cancer, preventing premature aging, and helping maintain an even skin tone.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_22">Drinking water instead of sugary drinks is beneficial for overall health. It aids in hydration, weight loss, improved physical performance, and reduced calorie intake, and helps prevent dental cavities and tooth decay.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_23">Choosing whole grains over refined grains can provide essential nutrients such as fiber, vitamins, and minerals. It can lower the risk of heart disease, stroke, obesity, and type 2 diabetes.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_24">Taking time for yourself is essential to prevent burnout. It allows you to decompress, improves mental health, boosts creativity, and enhances productivity and problem-solving skills.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_25">Including protein in every meal helps build and repair tissues, makes enzymes and hormones, and is a building block of bones, muscles, cartilage, skin, and blood. It also helps in satiety and weight management.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_26">Practicing gratitude can enhance well-being, increase happiness, reduce depression, and strengthen resilience. It fosters positive relationships and can improve physical health.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_27">Limiting alcohol consumption can have significant health benefits. It can lower the risk of liver disease, heart disease, stroke, cancer, and addiction. It also improves mental health and sleep quality.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_28">Seeking medical advice when needed is crucial for maintaining health. It ensures early detection of diseases, appropriate treatment, and advice on maintaining a healthy lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_29">Focusing on portion control helps manage calorie intake, promotes weight loss, and helps maintain a balanced diet. It is a key to healthy eating and preventing overeating.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_30">Celebrating health achievements, no matter how small, can motivate continued healthy behavior, boost self-esteem, and provide a sense of accomplishment in your health journey.</string>
    <string name="quote_desc_day_31">Incorporating a new healthy habit each month can lead to long-term health improvements. It encourages continuous growth and adaptation, making healthy living a dynamic and ongoing process.</string>
</resources>